I'm watching from across the room Chasing away
the afternoon gloom A private joke, a silent
glance A secret well-rehearsed dance The world
is loud, the world is fast A shadow that was never
cast Between the two of you, I see A perfect,
quiet harmony
It's in the unspoken words and space between the
lines
A secret language of your own designs More than a
feeling, more than a touch You never have to say
that much One heart that beats into part-time A
beautiful and perfect rhyme A bond the world
can't understand Held in the comfort of a hand He
stumbles
and you're there to brace A look of love upon your
face You feel his fear, you feel his pride With
nothing left to ever hide You are his anchor, he
is your sail A bond that will not ever fail I built
this house to keep you safe From every single
cruel strange
It's in the unspoken world, the space between
the lines
secret language of your own designs. More than a
feeling, more than a touch, you never have to say
that much. One heart that beats in two part time,
a beautiful and perfect rhyme. A bond the world
can understand Held in the comfort of a hand
It's in the unspoken world space between the
lines
A secret language of your own designs More than a
feeling, more than a touch You never have to say
that much One heart that beats into part-time A
beautiful and perfect rhyme